- oh yeah today you're going to learn
- alright hello everyone I'm
- some Advanced English vocabulary with the
- rolling solo on the loo later set
- film Avatar but before we do
- we have some news that took place today
- wanted to quickly let you know that if you're new here every
- surprise a sneaky little announcement
- we make fun lessons with your favorite movies and more
- from Apple they're not chilling they're not resting
- so that you can understand fast speaking natives without
- they're still putting stuff out granted
- getting lost without missing the jokes and without
- in a bit of a different way they didn't have any
- subtitles like Krishna who says that because of
- there was no big Fanfare of course
- our videos he feels like he can speak more like a native
- of the current state of planet
- and you can too all you have to do is hit that subscribe button and
- they did it virtually they did it from a distance
- hello so you don't miss any of our new lessons
- they did a No guest announcement
- and some people are talking about it so I figured
- I would check it out for myself and we could
- look at it together it is a new iPad
- Pro let's go ahead and roll this clip real quick we'll
- keep the music off but
- you see a similar design to the previous version but some new